jobsbridge.com 2010-05-07

# Jobsbridge - Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Valley Portals, Inc.'s (the "Company" or "We") job search Internet web site located at www.jobsbridge.com (the "website"). We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our respect for the privacy of our members and visitors to the website. 

## Overview

  * Company is committed to respecting the privacy of our users. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to the website and does not apply to information we collect in any other fashion.

The information gathered on this website may be shared within Company and its affiliated companies on a worldwide basis in order to deliver the products and services we offer to employers such as searches for job seekers or in order to undertake analysis of our database such as aggregate profiling of our users. "Affiliated companies" mean entities that control, are controlled by or are under common control with Company. 

The website contains links to other web sites over which we have no control. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other web sites to which you choose to link from our website. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information..

## Information Collection and Use

  * You can generally visit our website without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. However, in certain sections of this website, to use certain services, we may require you to create an account, or we may invite you to submit questions or comments or request information, subscribe to a newsletter, participate in surveys, questionnaires or contests, or message boards. Due to the nature of some of these activities, we may ask that you complete and submit an online form with personally identifiable information such as your name, username, email address, contact information, employment information. If you have created an account, you may opt to provide additional personally identifiable information in your profile such as your age, gender and employment information. Providing any additional personally identifiable information beyond what is required to create an account is optional. We may use your personally identifiable information to deliver certain services, products or information you have requested, verify your authority to enter certain password protected areas of the website, send you notices for services that you have used or that may be of interest to you, and improve the content and general administration of the website. We may receive your personally identifiable information from our partners that provide us with third-party services so that we can customize and improve the services that we may provide to you. Additionally, if you have elected to reveal your email address to other registered members, they will have access to and be able to use your email address.

## Other Usage of Information

  * We may also share aggregated anonymous information about visitors to this website with our clients, partners and other third parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to this website and how those visitors use the website. We may disclose your personally identifiable information and aggregate information to our partner entities that provide job networking services to us in order to confirm your accounts with such partner entities. Any organization to which we provide your personally identifiable information may not further distribute your personally identifiable information and may not use your information for commercial purposes. We will also disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to any other company or organization except we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which Company participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of Company's assets to which this website relates. Such successor entity shall be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

## Use of Cookies

  * We use "cookies" to help personalize and maximize your online experience and time online. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard drive by a web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize website pages, or register for services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information (such as user name, password and preferences). Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster and more accurate results and a more personalized website experience. When you return to the website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized. We also use cookies to track click streams and for load balancing. You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline all cookies if you prefer. Alternatively, you may be able to modify your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on this website. 

## Use of Web Beacons

  * This website may contain electronic images known as web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information; they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about our website usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides.   
You may not decline web beacons, however, they can be rendered ineffective by declining all cookies or modifying your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis.   
Third parties are not permitted to use Web beacons on this website. 

## Security

  * We may employ procedural and technological measures, consistent with industry practice. Such measures are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Company may use firewalls, internal restrictions, password protection, physical lock and key and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.

## Children

  * This website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under age 13. 

## Changes to Privacy Statement

  * If we decide to materially change our Privacy Statement for this website, we will post those changes through a prominent notice on the web site so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it. 

If at any time, you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Statement or believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Statement, please feel free to contact us. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly answer your question or resolve your problem. 

## Contact Information

  * Our business hours are 9:00am to 6:00pm PST, Monday - Friday 

Thank you for using Jobsbridge.com.
